Twin Buttes Mining and Smelting Company records, 1903-1969 (bulk 1903-1927)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IX: Miscellaneous Material, 1906-1926
  - Maps. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Location of water pumping station of Tucson in relation to the Twin Buttes Railroad, 1908
    Amended ground plan drawing, Morgan Mine, no date
    Glance Mine and Queen Mine, no date
  - Drawing of the school house at Twin Buttes. No Date (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Ledger. August 1906-March 1907 (Volume 68)
  - Ledger. 1907-1908 (Volume 69)
  - Journal. August 1906-March 1907 (Volume 69)